# **Edgars Puce**

#### **Personal Details**

Name: Edgars Puce

Date of Birth: 25/12/1987

Nationality: Latvian (European Union)

Korean visa: F-6

Email: <a href="mailto:puce.edgar@gmail.com">puce.edgar@gmail.com</a>
Phone Number: 010-2959-4518
GitHub: <a href="mailto:Edgar Puce GitHub">Edgar Puce GitHub</a>
LinkedIn: <a href="mailto:Edgar Puce LinkedIn">Edgars Puce LinkedIn</a>
Website: <a href="mailto:Edgar Puce Website">Edgar Puce Website</a>



#### **Personal Statement**

I am a passionate full-stack developer with 7+ years of experience, who loves to write code and solve problems. Coding is fun because you can create something new from nothing and see results very quickly. Sometimes I struggle to solve issues, but the more I try and fail, the more I can learn. And when I succeed, I feel proud of myself.

I have an F-6 visa and I can work in Korea without visa sponsorship. Also I have registered business in Korea and can work as a contractor/freelancer.

# **Work Experience**

August 2024 ~ Present: Shinsung NS Tech, South Korea

**Position:** Developer

#### **Responsibilities:**

- Created client side application for Hangang Bus information system for station and ship (LCD display). Technologies used: WPF (MVVM), Rest API.
- Created BIS (Bus Information System) for Siheung/Gwacheon/Gyeongju/Yangpyeong City (E-paper / LCD / LED displays). Technologies used: WPF (MVVM), MQTT, OPEN API (data.go.kr), TCP/IP
- Created an internal tool to monitor BIS application status. Technologies used: React, C# Rest Api running on Linux via Nginx
- Created BIS for Seoul to display bus routes and location real time. Technologies used: React, Nodejs, OPEN API
- Maintenance of existing applications

#### July 2021 ~ October 2023: 28Stone Consulting, Inc. Latvia/South Korea

Position: Developer

# Responsibilities:

- Worked on video recording and face recognition application for 6 months. Technologies used: Python, Electron.
- Created custom views in WPF for vendor application for 6 months.
- Worked on an internal project for company employee CV editing and generation application 1+ year. Technologies used: Angular, C#, AWS Lambda, AWS Cognito, AWS DynamoDB.

## March 2018 ~ June 2021: SEB Global Services, Riga, Latvia

**Position:** Developer

# **Responsibilities:**

- Developed AML related scenarios (SQL queries)
- Developed and deployed to production reporting solution (Required by Swedish Financial Police)
- Maintaining and improving developed reporting solution based on requirements
- Working on UI part for developed reporting solution to make it available to other departments within bank (React)
- Collaborate with other IT teams and product owners
- Maintained and updated vendor systems
- Maintained and developed QlikView application
- Automated manual processes of product owners

# June 2015 ~ June 2017: Tint a Car Korea Co., Ltd., Gyeonggi-do, South Korea

**Position:** Assistant Manager

## Responsibilities:

- Translating reports and documents from Korean to English
- Communication with Head office in Australia
- Meeting with international partners
- Helping with marketing
- Market research

# June 2012 – August 2014: Centra Convenience Co., Ltd., Dublin, Ireland

**Position:** Assistant Manager

# **Responsibilities:**

- Ordering products for the shop
- Training new staff
- Making reports for the Head Office (daily and weekly)
- Finance management and cash flow
- Meeting with sales representatives
- Running the shop on my own when manager is absent
- Staff management
- Working with software like Point Four, G.O.L.D and IRIS

## February 2008 – February 2011: Tele2 Shared Service Center, Riga, Latvia

**Position:** Billing Operations Specialist

#### **Responsibilities:**

- Responsible for running and monitoring daily operations (first line support) of billing and surrounding systems
- Ensure that processes are running smoothly and provide support to the local Billing offices in Tele2 countries in all Europe
- Resolve requests on demand and issues
- Communication with internal and external departments and Head Office in Sweden
- Carried out daily operational, monitoring and corrective functions within Billing Operations Team

## **Skills**

#### Hard skills:

- Programming: C#, JavaScript/Typescript (React, Nodejs, AngularJs), MongoDB, SQL. Some experience with: Java, Python
- Tools: VS 2022, VS Code, SSMS, GitHub, Git Bash, JIRA, Postman, Confluence, QlikView
- Other: JSON, XML, Rest API, TCP/IP, MQTT, WPF, xUnit.
- Some experience with: AWS (Lambda, Cognito, DynamoDB), Digital Ocean (Droplet, Serverless Function)
- Way of working: Agile, Scrum, Kanban, Program Increment (SAFe)
- Language skills: Russian, Latvian (Native), English (Fluent), Korean (TOPIK 2)

#### **Soft skills:**

- Great communication skills to build good relationship with customers
- Flexible regarding working hours and location
- Able to work under pressure and deliver results to deadlines
- Detail oriented
- Flexible and adaptable, able to work well individually and in a group
- Open minded and willing to learn
- Fast learner, loyal and reliable

# **Education**

Riga Technical University 2006 - 2010 (Latvia)

Bachelor degree in Telecommunications

Riga 94<sup>th</sup> High School 1994 – 2006 (Latvia)